Workers United Audiovisual Materials 6284 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Workers United Audiovisual Materials
1997-2005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Workers United
6284 AV
3.78 cubic feet
3.8 linear ft.
Audio cassette tapes, video cassette tapes, CDs.
8820011
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 24, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, May 08, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Workers United
8820011
- How to Defend Your Rights: Immigrant Garment Workers Unite -- English Version (Box 1, Folder 1)
- How to Defend Your Rights: Immigrant Garment Workers Unite -- English Version (Box 1, Folder 2)
- How to Defend Your Rights: Immigrant Garment Workers Unite -- English Version (Box 1, Folder 3)
- How to Defend Your Rights: Immigrant Garment Workers Unite -- Chinese Version (Box 1, Folder 4)
- How to Defend Your Rights: Immigrant Garment Workers Unite -- Chinese Version (Box 1, Folder 5)
- How to Defend Your Rights: Immigrant Garment Workers Unite -- Chinese Version (Box 1, Folder 6)
- A.E. Stanley Strike in Decatur, Illinois - ACTWU Support (Box 1, Folder 7)
- A.E. Stanley Strike in Decatur, Illinois - ACTWU Support (Box 1, Folder 8)
- June 1995 Rally of ILGWU's Worker Justice Center in Sunset Park, Brooklyn (Box 1, Folder 9)
- June 1995 Rally of ILGWU's Worker Justice Center in Sunset Park, Brooklyn (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Is There a Sweatshop in Your Future? (English/Spanish) For Internal Union Education (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Is There a Sweatshop in Your Future? (English/Spanish) For Internal Union Education (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Heritage of Labor (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Repetitive Strain Injuries, esp. carpal tunnel syndrome - W. Chinese voice-over (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Rally for Sweat Shop in Manhattan (Box 1, Folder 15)
- ILGWU Organizing Dept. Presents: Memorable Media Moments in Labor History (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Sweat Shop Campaign Rally in Manhattan (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Working in the USA: Know Your Rights - Feb. 1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Unite! Members Love New York (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Aug. 28, 1998 Chinatown Rally (Box 1, Folder 20)
- PROP 187 - Mon.-Wed. Level III News prog. (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Mon-Wed Level I and IV Prop. 187 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- ILGWU "Count Me In - A Bridge to Citizenship TRT" 9/23/94, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- UNITE Immigration Project "Count Me In: A Bridge to Citizenship" (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Count Me In - A Bridge to Citizenship (Box 1, Folder 25)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union "It's About Jobs" (Box 1, Folder 26)
- ILGWU: UNITE and Fight (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Trabajadores de Domsey: Ustedes Son El Sindicato (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Memorable Moments in Labor History (Box 1, Folder 29)
- ILGWU Video Catalogue (Box 1, Folder 30)
- UNITE New Members -- English and Spanish (Box 1, Folder 31)
- 48 Hours on the Fashion Industry (Box 2, Folder 1)
- STOP SWEATSHOPS! The video (Box 2, Folder 2)
- STOP SWEATSHOPS! The video (Box 2, Folder 3)
- STOP SWEATSHOPS! The video (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Sweatshops and the Triangle Fire (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Chinatown Garment Factory (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Channel 2 News on Sweatshops in NYC (Box 2, Folder 7)
- AFL Roll Ins. Immigration (Box 2, Folder 8)
- UNITE "July 29th - Lobby Day Against Sweatshops" English and Spanish (Box 2, Folder 9)
- UNITE! Because Every Vote Counts! (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Why Your Vote Makes a Difference Spanish (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Mickey Mouse Goes to Haiti (Box 2, Folder 12)
- ESL-Prop 187 T/Th Classes (Box 2, Folder 13)
- We Do The Work Leaving Home Short Version (Box 2, Folder 14)
- We Do The Work Show 309 Sewing Our Future (Box 2, Folder 15)
- We Do The Work Sewing Our Future (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Surviving the bottom line with Hendrick Smith (Box 2, Folder 17)
- How Legal Immigrants Strengthen America (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Frontline: Is Walmart Good for America? (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Is There a Sweatshop in Your Future? (Box 2, Folder 20)
- 1995 Union Christmas Party (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Something to Hide (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Something to Hide (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Pioneers and Paper Sons Chinese Immigration History (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Labor Rally in Chinatown (Box 2, Folder 25)
- United Farm Workers of America "NO GRAPES" English Version (Box 2, Folder 26)
- The ILGWU Worker Center in Brooklyn (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Silent Danger Chinese Version (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Mademoiselle an ILG Shop (Box 2, Folder 29)
- The Writing Program (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Your Move Your Pain Chinese Version (Box 2, Folder 31)
- ILGWU Video Catalogue (Box 2, Folder 32)
- NY Retirees Art Show 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- UNITE HERE! Hurricane Katrina Relief (Box 4, Folder 1)
- UNITE HERE! Working Together for a Better Future, November 2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Local 23-25 - title of tape is in Chinese Characters, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Local 23-25 - title of tape is in Chinese Characters, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Local 23-25 - title of tape is in Chinese Characters, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Our American Way of Life, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Citizenship (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Our American Way of Life (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Cutting - Rischerto/Gustavo (Box 12, Folder 1)
- "We Do the Work" - Bread + Roses, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Chinese Lunch - Houston -- 9/19/1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Graduation Tape - ILG -- For: Rosa (Malcolm Dodd's) (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Sam / Lana (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Lana (most of title is in Chinese characters) (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Allied Fibers Inc. - 7/21/1993 (Box 18, Folder 1)